auditiondate.in 2019-03-23

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Of AuditionDate.In**

The  privacy of visitors is very importance to **AuditionDate**. Taking care of your personal information is our responsibilities and we do. This Privacy policy is about how we collected and used your personal information.

**PPC Advertisement Policy**

To serve ads AuditionDate.In use third party advertising company. Some of them like Adsense. They uses DART cookie to serve advertisement based on user interest and previous interaction. But user can stop this by visiting the [Google Adsense and Content Network Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

User can also disable cookies if they want by using their own browser options.

**Copyright Policy**

All contents on this website is Copyright to AuditionDate.In. If you want to use content of our website ,you first must ask us and you also have to provide credit links on the pages you have copied or used the content of AuditionDate.In

**Comment Moderation Policy**

We likes comments and thoughts, but any comments which is abusive, racial or any way hurting anyone opinion will never be entertained. We always moderate the comments to maintain the integrity of visitors.

**Disclaimer**

Images & videos on this website are copyright to their respective owner.

**_Note- The shows listed on our website is copyright to their respective owner, all right reserved to their respective owners. _** ** _Auditiondate.in is not a partner or host of any such shows listed on our website. We are just providing information about this shows._**

### Like Us on Facebook For Audition News
